威尔 · 森特斯: 我们走吧。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Let's go.
让我们看看，因为这是一条复直线。
Let's see that because it's
gonna be a complex line.
但是从我们的第一句台词开始，我们想放一段时间，瑞安。
But starting with our first line here,
we wanna put on for a while, Ryan.
我向你道歉，莱恩。
I apologize Ryan.
莱恩，我们在第一行代码里做什么？
Ryan, what are we doing here
in line one of our code?
Ryan: 声明一个函数显示。
&gt;&gt; Ryan: Declaring a function display.
声明一个函数显示，精确地和
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Declaring
a function display, exactly and
存储在全局存储器中。
storing it in global memory.
在那里，功能显示被存储。
There it is,
the function display is stored.
太好了，谢谢你，瑞恩。
Excellent, thank you, Ryan.
第二行，左手边。
Line two, left hand side.
伊森，我们先从左边开始,
Ethan, what do we do on
the left hand side here first,
先说点简单的，伊森。
just a sort of easy bit here first Ethan.
伊森: 声明一个常量未来数据。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Declaring
a constant future data.
威尔 · 森特斯: 没错，未来的数据，我从来不知道美国人说的是数据还是
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Exactly, future data,
I never know whether Americans say data or
数据。
data.
但是好吧，现在还没有初始化。
But all right, so
it's uninitialized for now.
顺便说一句，这告诉我们右边的 fetch 调用,
Already by the way, this tells us that
fetch call on the right hand side,
在背景中触发东西的 facade 函数,
the facade function that
triggers stuff in the background,
它还必须在 JavaScript 中做些什么。
it must also do something in JavaScript.
因为它在 JavaScript 中的结果
Because the result of it in
JavaScript at that moment
储存在左手边。
is stored on the left hand side.
因此，在某种程度上，它必须是双管齐下的，两个结果。
So it must be two pronged in some way,
two consequences.
所以，未来的数据。
So, future data.
在这里，futureData 将是 JavaScript 的结果
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Here it is, futureData
will be the result in JavaScript
的结果的一半，它的 JavaScript 控制台。
of half of the consequence of fetch,
its JavaScript console.
记住，右边的输出存储在左边。
Remember, the output of the right hand
side stored on the left-hand side.
但是这是一个假想的 JavaScript 函数，它是一个 facade。
But this is a pretend JavaScript function,
it's a facade.
它会为我们做一些 JavaScript 的工作，但是它也会自动地,
It's gonna do some JavaScript work for
us, but it's also, automatically,
但它也会在后台做一些工作，网页浏览器。
but it's also gonna do some work in
the background, the web browser.
这就是我们的网址。
There it is, off to our URL.
所以，让我们先来做 JavaScript consequences。
So, let's do it JavaScript
consequence first.
它将立即在 JavaScript 中返回。
It is going to immediately
in JavaScript return out.
让我用我的粉红色作为我的特殊对象。
Let me use my pink here for
my special object.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 我的特殊对象。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: My special object.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 一个承诺的对象,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: A promise object,
它只是一个通过获取在 JavaScript 中自动创建的对象。
it's just an object automatically
created in JavaScript by fetch.
它有两个属性。
It has two properties.
我们等会儿再看他们的表现。
We're gonna see what they do later on.
没有定义的值，没有任何东西存储在上面。
Value which is undefined,
nothing stored on it yet.
你可能已经在想，等等，我去拿些数据回来。
Already you might be thinking,
hold on, I'm gonna get some data back.
我想知道这些在 JavaScript 中会出现在什么地方。
I wonder where that's gonna perhaps
show up back in JavaScript.
一个被称为满足的财产。
And a property called on fulfilled.
结果是隐藏的，但是非常重要的是一个空数组。
It's gonna turn out to be hidden but
super important which is an empty array.
如果右边的输出被存储在
And that object is gonna be stored if the
output of the right hand side is stored on
左手边被撕破了，要存放在哪里？
the left hand side and so torn,
it's gonna be stored where?
演讲者4: 未来数据。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: In the futureData.
Will Sentance: 在 futureData 标签中，在 futureData 标识符中，精确地。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: In the futureData label,
in the futureData identifier, exactly.
我们抓住它，把它插入，威尔 · 森特斯: 未来数据,
We grab it, we stick it into,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: FutureData,
就是这个，value，我可以听到 Tana 开始担心
there it is, value,
I can hear Tana getting worried about how
我带着我的承诺目标来到这里。
far right I've gone here with
the my promise object here.
我们走吧,
On, there we go,
是一个大的，空的数组。
on fulfilled is a big, empty array.
就是这样，伙计们。
There it is, folk.
那么好吧,
So, well,
看看这个，我要去建立一些网页浏览器的背景资料。
look at this, I'm about to go and
set up some background web browser stuff.
我忘了我安排好了吗？
Do I forget I set it up?
当然不是，我有一个可爱的小承诺对象在这里提醒我
Well, of course not, I've got a lovely
little promise object here that reminds me
我在后台设置了一些东西。
that I've set something
up in the background.
但现在，事情变得有趣起来。
But now, things get interesting.
另一个后果是什么呢
Where is fetch's other
consequence on the board to our
空间安置专家-伊森: [笑]
specialist in spatial placement-
&gt;&gt; Ethan: [LAUGH]
威尔 · 森特斯: 伊森，我们的
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Ethan, where is our
其他... 不不不,
other- no, no, no,
你不用...-我们的另一个后果是什么？
you don't have to- where is our other
consequence of fetch on the board?
伊森: 在网页浏览器里。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: It's in the web browser.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 确切地说，是在网页浏览器里。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's in the web browser,
exactly.
看看这个，两个尖头，[声音] ，对吗？
Look at this, two prongs, [SOUND], right?
另一个后果就是网页浏览器。
And the other consequence
is in the web browser.
威尔 · 森特斯: 这就对了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: There you go.
在浏览器里就是我们要设置的地方,
In the web browser, there it is,
where we are gonna set up,
现在我有时称这个 XHR 为 XML HTTP 请求，它来自于概念
now I sometimes call this XHR which is XML
HTTP request, that comes from the notion
Xml 是我们在互联网上发送消息的数据格式。
of XML being the format of the data by
which we send messages over the Internet.
Http 是我们如何在浏览器和浏览器之间发送消息的一组规则
HTTP being the set of rules for
how we send messages between a browser and
一个服务器，一个 HTTP 协议。
a server, an HTTP protocol.
并请求意义，我想得到的东西。
And request meaning, I wanna get stuff.
但是我们只是把它作为一个网络来讨论,
But we'll just talk about it
more generally as a network,
这意味着通过互联网，请求。
that means over the Internet, request.
这就是了，一个网络请求。
There it is, a Network Request.
这就是我们将要在网页浏览器中使用的功能。
That's the feature we're gonna
use in the web browser down here.
就是这样，网络请求，威尔 · 森特斯: 就是这样。
There it is, Network Request,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: There it is.
我们大概在0毫秒内完成这个过程。
And we're doing this at roughly I guess,
zero milliseconds.
我们倾向于从那里开始。
We tend to start there.
顺便说一下，看看这个五个字母的单词已经做了多少工作。
By the way, already, look how much
that five letter word has done.
而我们，还没有完成。
And we, not done yet.
对 Twitter 的网络请求需要知道什么重要信息 Jeff,
A network request to Twitter needs to
know what important information Jeff,
从什么被传送到接收,
from what's being passed into fetch,
它需要知道哪些重要信息才能知道去哪里？
what important information does it
need to know to know where to go?
杰夫: 地址。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: The address.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，这里有两部分。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah and
that's sorta got two parts here.
上面有域名,
It's got the domain name,
它会告诉我们在互联网上应该去哪台电脑，在哪个 IP 地址。
that's gonna tell us which computer on the
Internet to go to, at which IP address.
一旦我们在那里着陆，这条路径，就会告诉我们这些电脑的哪一部分
And once we land there, the path, that's
gonna tell us which bit of that computers
存储数据，我们要去哪条路线，并从中获取数据。
store of data, which route that
we're gonna go and grab data from.
这两个部件会被传送到我们的网络请求。
Those two pieces are gonna be passed
to our Network Request down here.
所以我们必须有我们的推特网站,
So we're gotta have our twitter.com,
我们会找到自己的路。
and we're gonna have our path.
我们可以通过互联网从浏览器发送数据，或者我们也可以要求数据。
And we can send data from a browser over
the Internet, or we can also ask for data.
所以我们可以说，嘿，我有一个新的推特，我想让你保存。
So we can say, hey,
I've got a new tweet I want you to save.
我们使用什么方法呢？
What's a method we use for that?
我们用什么 HTTP 方法发送数据，发布。
What's the HTTP method we
use to send data, to post.
观众: (笑)威尔 · 森塔斯: 好了。
&gt;&gt; Audience: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: There we go.
亲爱的。
Dear.
好了，各位。
All right, well everybody.
太棒了，是的，发表了，干得好。
[LAUGH] Brilliant, yes, post, well done.
没错 post。
Exactly, post.
如果我们想要的主要是获取数据推文呢？
What about when we wanted is
mainly be getting data tweets?
好的，对-观众: (笑)
Okay, right-
&gt;&gt; Audience: [LAUGH]
威尔 · 森塔斯: 这太愚蠢了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: This is just silly.
好吧。
All right, well.
观众: (笑)威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们会重拍的。
&gt;&gt; Audience: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We'll reshoot that.
如果我想检索数据怎么办？
What if I want to retrieve data?
讲者4: Get。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Get.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 得到。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Get.
瑞恩: 走吧。
&gt;&gt; Ryan: Get.
威尔 · 森特斯: 干得好，伙计们。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Get, well done, people.
留在里面。
Leave it in.
听众: (笑)威尔 · 森塔斯: 那么,
&gt;&gt; Audience: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: So,
我们这里没有明确说明。
we didn't specify that here.
这是因为 fetch 默认为 get。
That's because fetch defaults to get.
它会默认为。
It's gonna default to get.
如果我们想 Post，我们实际上可以作为另一个参数传入
If we wanted to Post, we can
actually pass in as another argument
获取一个充满选择的对象。
to fetch an object full of options.
这意味着我们需要了解更多关于如何使用 fetch 的信息。
That means kind of extra information
about how we wanna use fetch.
我们可以设置发布的方法。
And we can set the method to be posting.
但是我们会默认从这个五个字母的单词,
But we're gonna default to get all by
the way from this five letter word,
有点疯狂。
kind of crazy.
这就是我们正在使用的功能。
That's the feature we're using.
完成了吗？
Is it complete?
好吧，这都是第二种，但是
Well, that's all kind of second, but
完成后，威尔 · 森坦斯: 我们该怎么办？
on completion,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: What are we gonna do?
它是在零毫秒时完成的吗？
Is it complete at zero milliseconds?
上网需要多长时间？
How long does it take to be
able to go to the Internet?
上网需要零毫秒吗？
Does it take zero milliseconds to
be able to go to the Internet?
没有所以是完整的吗 Kayla？
No, so is it complete, Kayla?
没有 威尔 · 森塔斯: 绝对没有。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: No.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's definitely no.
完全正确。
Spot on.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 事实上，在我们开始完成工作之前,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Actually, before we
move on to what we do on completion,
我们开始吧。
let's get it started.
我们开始工作吧。
Let's get the work started.
所以它会通过互联网发送信息,
So it's gonna send a message
off to over the Internet,
它开始通过互联网向 Twitter 总部发送 HTTP 消息。
it starts to send a HTTP message over
the Internet to Twitter's headquarters.
他们在那里，Twitter 总部，就在那里。
There they are, Twitter HQ, there it is.
我从来不知道我是在这里画电脑还是有点像办公室，但是
I never know whether I'm drawing a
computer here or kinda like an office, but
让我们保持模棱两可。
let's leave it ambiguous.
实际上，那是，威尔 · 森坦斯: 可能是
Actually that's,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Could be
一间办公室，不是吗？
an office, couldn't it?
可能有点有意思。
Could be, it's kind of, interesting, yeah.
听众: (笑)威尔 · 森塔斯: 一个观察,
&gt;&gt; Audience: [LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: One observation,
在互联网上，开始的时间是0毫秒,
there it is, over the Internet,
that's started off as zero milliseconds,
它会说，嘿，Twitter，我需要去获取数据。
off it runs saying, hey, Twitter,
I need to go and get data.
好吧，但目前还没有完成。
All right, but
it's not complete at this point.
顺便说一下，所有这些都是通过这五个字母完成的。
By the way,
all this done by these five letters.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 我要回到我的故事
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I'm gonna
go back to my story about my
跨西伯利亚铁路的雇主。
employer at the transsiberian railway.
在互联网上到处都是，怎么样？
All over the Internet, how about that?
好吧，那么，在网上，是的，那么,
All right, so, at the Internet, yeah, so,
一旦完工，会发生什么？
on completion though,
what is gonna happen?
如果你还记得我说的暂停当我们设置一个背景功能时,
Well, if you remember when I said timeout,
when we set up a background feature,
我们这里有一个函数可以在 Call Stack 上自动运行,
we had a function here,
that would auto run on the Call Stack,
我们把 Call Stack 放在这里,
let's actually put our Call Stack
in here at this point,
将自动运行的调用堆栈，将森坦斯: 在
would auto run on the Call Stack,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: On
完成后台任务。
completion of the background task.
但是有人看到一个函数在这里被解析为 fetch 吗？
But anyone see a function
being parsed into fetch here?
没有，所以我们的双重功能
No, so our two pronged features or
在 web 浏览器功能方面，他们采用了不同的模式。
facade functions for web browser features,
they take a different model.
他们说，不是传入一个函数,
They say,
instead of having a function passed in,
你可以看到这个漂亮的东西
you've got this pretty object
that's kind of keeping track
我们在背景里设置了一些东西。
of the fact that we set
something up in the background.
所以人们会使用它。
So one will use it.
实际上，当数据返回时，我们用紫色表示返回的数据
And in fact, when that data comes back,
let's use purple for my return data from
推特，当它完成的时候，它会带回一些推文。
Twitter, when it does complete,
it's gonna come back with some tweets.
他们称之为响应对象。
They call it response object.
我们要简化它
We're gonna simplify it and
只要给它一连串的推特，无论它什么时候回来。
just give it the string of the tweet,
whenever it comes back.
这能去哪儿呢？
Where could that go?
如果你有什么想法，请举手
Raise your hand if you've got an idea
我们如何将这些数据返回到作业中，并返回到 JavaScript 中。
how we could get that data back into jobs
where it could go back in JavaScript.
好的，让我们请凯拉。
Yeah, let's have Kayla.
是这样的我不记得你叫它什么了,
&gt;&gt; Kayla: It goes,
I can't remember what you called it,
在威尔 · 森塔斯的一些东西上: 它不是
the on, something on the
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's not
放到那个数组里。
into that array.
马克，你要不要短一点？
Mark, do you wanna take this short?
马克: 进入价值？
&gt;&gt; Mark: Into the value?
进入价值属性。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Into the value property.
对了，顺便说一下，你说，凯拉，在那里，进入价值属性。
So right, by the way, you said, Kayla,
there, into the value property.
因为取物有两个尖端，它们紧密地连接在一起。
Because fetch has these two prongs,
and they are intimately connected.
这样当后台任务完成时,
Such that when the background
task completes,
它会粘在那个立即返回的物体上。
it's going to stick into that
immediately returned out object.
无论何时发生这种情况，都可能是明天，非常，非常慢的网络请求。
Whenever this happens, could be tomorrow,
very, very slow network request.
但随时都有可能,
But could be any time,
存储在 futureData 中的对象有一个漂亮的
that object that got stored into
futureData has a beautiful little, look at
空的未定义绑定属性可以存储什么？
that, empty undefined binding property,
into which what could be stored Kayla?
回应。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: The response.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 回复数据，来自 Twitter 的数据,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The response data,
the data that comes back from Twitter,
她说对了。
she's spot on.
它将返回到这个值属性中。
It will go back into this value property.
特别是 Matt,
So specifically, Matt,
什么样的确切位置，我可以把它放在这里的完成位？
what's the exact sort of locations I can
put it in the on completion bit here?
马特: 它在未来数据中。
&gt;&gt; Matt: It's in the futureData.
未来数据，嗯，未来数据,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: FutureData,
mm-hm, futureData.,
马特: 点值。
&gt;&gt; Matt: Dot value.
点值，是的，没错,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Dot value, yeah exactly,
值会随着数据更新,
futureData.value will be
updated with the data,
正如凯拉所说，从对互联网讲话。
just as Kayla said,
from speaking to the Internet.
是的，她说得很对，也要谢谢马特。
Yeah, she's spot on,
thank you to Matt as well.
好了，各位，我们能不能稍微谈谈那五个字母的作用？
All right people, can we just talk about
for a second what those five letters did?
我的天，他们设置在背景里，他们对着互联网说话
My goodness, they set up in
the background, they speak to the Internet
它需要所有的信息，去取回正确的数据。
with all the information it needs
to go and get the right data back.
但是他们也在 JavaScript 中设置了一个小的占位符对象，称为
But they also set up in JavaScript
a little placeholder object known as
一个承诺的对象。
a promise object.
只是一个普通的对象，但有一些自动内置的属性。
Just a regular object but
with some auto built in properties.
存储在 futureData 中，就是这样。
And that was stored into futureData,
there it is.
它有一个空值属性，它在 on fulfilled 属性上有一个空数组,
It has an empty value property, it has an
empty array on the on fulfilled property,
顺便说一句，这是一个隐藏的财产。
which by the way we'll
see as a hidden property.
但它与正在进行的背景工作密切相关。
But it's intimately linked to
the background work being done.
这样当背景工作完成后,
Such that when the background
work finishes,
可能是200毫秒，300毫秒，谁知道呢？
could be 200 milliseconds from now,
300, who knows?
对象的 value 属性将被[ SOUND ]更新。
That value property of the object
is gonna be [SOUND] updated.